Sadinsky, Matthew Collection of Public Employment Documents 5771
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Matthew Sadinsky Collection of Public Employment Documents
1970-1984
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sadinsky, Matthew
5771
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5702266
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 07, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 02, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective bargaining; Industrial relations; Civil service; New York (N.Y.) -- Officials and employees; Sadinsky, Matthew.; New York (N.Y.). Board of Education
5702266
- UFT, Salaries/ IOS A Taylor Law Probst, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Institute of Public Employment & Schools, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Legislative Drafting Manual - Colorado Drafting Office, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Misc. 1970's, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Labor Law Reform Testimony 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- UFT, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Board of Education; New York State & The U.S. Economy, 1976-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- More Effective Management is Needed to Improve the Quality of The Summer Youth Employment Program, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- New York State, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- State Data, Other States, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Dissertation, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- United Federation of Teachers, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- UFT Memos, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- NYS Taylor Law Bills 78 Session, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- NYS Taylor Law Bills 78 Session, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)